https://www.usg.com/content/usgcom/en/legal-information/privacy-policy.html

We use cookies to provide a personalized site experience. By continuing to use and browse this site, you agree to our Privacy Policy.
Password
Forgot your password?
Sign In
Keep Me Signed In
New to USG?
Create an account
Employee Sign-in |
Careers Website Sign-in
You're All Set
Welcome back! You are now signed in.
Back to the site
Forgot Password
Please enter the email address you used to create the account. We'll send you a link that lets you create a new password.
Email Address
Send password reset email
Back to Sign-in
You're All Set
Please check your email. Click the link in the email to create a new password.
Back to the site
Sign In
Oops!
It looks like you entered an employee email address, but this is the customer sign-in. Use the link below instead.
You're All Set
Success! Your password has been updated.
Back to the site
Change Password
Current Password
New Password
Your password must be at least 8 characters, including at least 1 number and at least 1 capital letter.
Confirm New Password
Change Password
You're All Set
Success! Your password has been updated.
Retiree Inquiries
Customer Service (Sales)
Danoline™ Acoustical Gypsum Inspirational Book
Drywall Ceilings Never Sounded so good.
Sheetrock® Interior Finishings Catalog
The Only Wallboard Specifiable for Sustainability.
Design Studio
An off-site air barrier can help on the job site.
Digital tools that make a difference
Redesigned submittal builder and product comparison tools will make your job easier
Privacy
USG does collect certain information about the users of our web site. Collection and use of this information is governed by USG’s Privacy Policy which is set forth below:
Privacy Policy
USG Corporation ("USG") supports the highest standards of integrity for every online visitor. When you register at the USG web site, our goal is to respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth how we handle information we obtain from you and learn about you when you visit our web site, including:
The choices that are available to you regarding how the information is used and to whom it is disseminated; Your rights to access and correct or update your personally-identifiable information; and Our pledge to have reasonable security procedures that are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control.
If you live outside the United States (including in the European Economic Area (“EE”) and Switzerland (“CH”) collectively the “EEA/CH”), and you use this site or provide us with your personal information directly via this site, your information will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By using this site or giving us your personal information, you are directly transferring your personal information to us in the United States. You agree and consent to our collection, transfer, and processing of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You are solely responsible for compliance with any data protection or privacy obligations in your jurisdiction when you use this site or provide us with your personal information. Regardless of where we transfer your information, we still protect your information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.
Information We Collect and How We Use It
USG collects two types of information about you when you visit our site: personal information (including, by way of example only, your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address) and non-personal, aggregate information (such as information regarding the pages on our site that you have visited and your IP address).
Personally Identifiable Information
The only personally identifying information we collect and store about you is the information that you choose to provide to us.
Electronic Mail
We will also gather your personally-identifiable information when you send us an e-mail. We will use this information to respond to your e-mail. We may also use the information to send you notifications about our service.
Business Partners/Professional Visitors
Business partners and professional visitors requesting access to specialized content areas of this web site may be required to provide identifying information.
Sharing Your Information
We may share your personally-identifiable information within USG.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
The USG web site may collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit, such as type of browser, operating system, domain name, or IP address. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the web. Web servers — the big computers that "serve" up web pages — automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you visit pages on USG's web site, our servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information. This means that your session will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. IP address information is used only to improve the service of the USG site, and is then discarded at the end of each session on our site. USG also collects information through "referrers" and various environmental variables. A "referrer" is information the web browser passes along to USG's web server that references the URL from which you came. "Environmental variables" include, among other things, the domain from which you access the Internet, the time you accessed our web site, type of web browser and operating system or platform used, the Internet address of the web site you left to visit USG, the names of the pages you visit while at our web site, and the Internet address of the web site you then visit. We collect all of this information to allow us to detect broad demographic trends, to provide information tailored to your interests and to enhance your experience on USG's web site. USG may store "referrer" information for a limited period of time prior to deleting this information. Analytical Tools: USG and our third party service providers collect information about you, your device, and your use of the web site through analytical tracking tools and methods (collectively, “Analytical Tools”). Analytical Tools collect information such as operating system type, IP address, browser type and language, mobile device ID, device hardware type, the web site or application visited or used before or after accessing USG’s web site, the parts of the web site accessed, the length of time spent on a page or using a feature, and access times for a webpage or feature. These Analytical Tools help us analyze how users use the web site, including what features they use, what pages they visit, and what other sites or applications they used prior to or after visiting the web site.
Profiling
To help us improve our web site and to ensure that we make every effort to provide you with information and offers that are of interest to you, we may merge your personally-identifiable information with click-stream data and other data we have (including cookies and offline data). We will provide notice of this, as well as an opportunity to opt-out of it, at the time and place of information collection and before data is entered on our system. We may also develop a non-identifiable profile on you based on the pages within our site that you visit.
Links
This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected when you visit our web site.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Special Policy Regarding Information from Children Under Thirteen
This web site is not targeted to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly request personally identifiable information from any child under the age of 13 without parental consent. When we do receive such information, we delete it as soon as we discover it and do not use it or share it with third parties.
Choice
USG provides the following choices regarding the use of your information:
You may choose not to provide us with any contact information. You may set your browser to erase cookies that have already been placed on your hard drive. You may email us at usg_webmaster@usg.com if you wish to have any personally identifiable information changed or deleted.
Security
We make every effort to have reasonable security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. If you have any questions about the security at our Website, you can send an email to usg_webmaster@usg.com.
Notice to California Residents under the California Consumer Privacy Act
The California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) imposes certain obligations on companies that collect “personal information” from California residents (also called “consumers” under the CCPA).  This notice describes how USG collects, uses and discloses personal information, as well as the rights and choices of California consumers.  USG refers to USG Corporation on behalf of itself and its affiliates, United States Gypsum Company, USG Interiors, LLC, USG Ceilings Plus, LLC, CGC Inc., and USG Mexico S.A. de C.V.  The reference to “you” or “your” in this disclosure refers to California residents. In the past twelve months, USG has collected personal information from the following categories of California residents (or “consumers”):  ·         Customers who purchase USG products. ·         Visitors who register on our website or make inquiries through our website. ·         Employees as necessary to the employment relationship and to process insurance, compensation and other benefits. ·         Vendors or suppliers of goods or services to USG. ·         Job applicants. Below is a chart indicating by a checkmark the category of personal information that may be collected from each of the types of California residents.  A description of what may be included in each category is listed at the end of this disclosure.
A description of the types of personal information included in each category is at the end of this disclosure. USG may use or disclose the categories of personal information collected for one or more of the following purpose(s):A description of the types of personal information included in each category is at the end of this disclosure. ·         To fulfill the reason for which you provided the personal information. ·         To provide you with information, products, or services.  For example, if you provide USG with your mailing address for USG to send you warranty information, we will use that provided address to send you the requested information. ·         To provide you with notices and email alerts. ·         To enforce USG’s contractual rights. ·         To improve the USG.com website and provide relevant content to you. ·         To conduct or evaluate a transaction such as a merger, divestiture, dissolution, or other sale of assets, whether as part of a bankruptcy or in the normal course of business, in which personal information held by USG is among the assets to be transferred. ·         Reason(s) listed in any notice(s) provided to you at the time of collecting your personal information. USG may disclose personal information for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties: ·         Companies under common ownership. ·         Service providers, as necessary to transact business with customers, to process job applications, or to provide benefits and compensation (such as payroll, insurance and retirement benefits). ·         Third parties to whom you or your agent(s) authorize USG to disclose your personal information. In the preceding 12 months, USG has disclosed the following categories of personal information for a business purpose: ·         Identifiers ·         Personal information ·         Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law ·         Commercial information ·         Biometric information ·         Internet/network activity ·         Geolocation data ·         Professional and employment-related data ·         Non-public education information ·         Inferences drawn from other personal information See below for a description of what personal information is included in each category. In the preceding 12 months, USG has not sold any personal information of California residents, including minors under the age of 16.  USG does not intend to sell personal information of California residents to third parties. Under certain circumstances California residents have the right to request that USG disclose the personal information of the California resident that USG has collected, used, disclosed, or sold in the twelve months preceding the request.  The CCPA requires us to respond to such requests within 45 days.  The right to request does not apply to certain categories of personal information that are collected pursuant to the employment relationship or certain benefits information as set forth in the CCPA. Under certain circumstances, California residents have the right to request that USG delete the personal information that USG has collected from the resident after receiving a verifiable request from that resident.  The right to deletion does not apply to personal information we collect that is necessary to complete a transaction for which the information was obtained, provide a product or service to the resident, perform a contract, comply with a legal obligation, or to personal information that is collected in connection with the employment relationship or subject to HIPPA, among other things.  To make a request to disclose or delete, please contact us using the form or at 855-562-2420. Under certain circumstances, the CCPA allows California residents to opt out of providing personal information.  California residents have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment by USG for the exercise of their privacy rights under CCPA. Although USG does not sell the personal information it collects from California residents, California residents have the right under certain circumstances to direct us not to sell their personal information.  California residents may submit their requests to exercise their rights under the CCPA to us by: ·         Using the online request form ·         Calling us at 855-562-2420 Only you or an agent authorized to act on your behalf may make a verifiable request under the CCPA on your behalf.  In addition, you may make a verifiable request on behalf of your minor child. For more information regarding the rights of California consumers under the CCPA, please see the CCPA Fact Sheet. This privacy policy was last updated on December 19, 2019. Contact USG for more information: If you have any questions or concerns about USG’s privacy policies and practices, please contact us at the online request form listed above or by phone at 855-562-2420. Below is a description of how the CCPA defines the categories of personal information.  This does not mean that USG collects every type of personal information that is included in the category:
Need Help?
Contact Us
Media Inquiries
Investor Relations
Retiree Inquiries
Customer Service (Sales)
Terms and Conditions for USG Sales/Terms and Conditions for USG POs
©2020 USG Corporation. All rights reserved.
